inspireyourway.com 2015-06-02

# Privacy Policy

At Inspireyourway, the privacy of our esteemed visitors is very important. This privacy policy document explains the amount of personal information [www.inspireyourway.com](http://www.inspireyourway.com/) collect and what are the process involved and how it is used.

##### **Log Files**

We uses log files to collect information about visitor’s internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser details Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, date/time stamp and analyze trends, track users’ movement throughout the website.

The above mentioned information cannot be used in anyway to collect user’s personal information.

##### **Cookies and Web Beacons**

[www.inspireyourway.com](http://www.inspireyourway.com/) uses cookies to collect information about visitor’s interests and preferences, tracks user’s movement throughout the website, their browser details and few more informations which **do not include their personal information like their address, personal documents, credit card details and other secret information.**

**Cookies are helpful**[www.inspireyourway.com](http://www.inspireyourway.com/) **as it helps us to understand our beloved visitors’ interests which will help us to improve our website content.**

**DoubleClick DART Cookie** .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.inspireyourway.com](http://www.inspireyourway.com/).  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.inspireyourway.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include….  
_Google Adsense_  
_Chitika_  
_Kontera_  
_Infolinks_

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://wrestlerspeaks.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.inspireyourway.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.inspireyourway.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**_If you have any queries regarding the use of cookies feel free to contact us or email us[hello@inspireyourway.com](mailto:hello@inspireyourway.com) any time. We will be more than happy to get back to you within 24 hours. _**
